THE FIRST QUEST REVEAL
The first quest will unlock now.
Your first quest is…
the sunrise
from Taebaeksan Mountain.
What?
WATCHING THE SUNRISE FROM TAEBAEKSAN
…from Taebaeksan Mountain.
What?
The sunrise?
What do you mean?
TAEBAEKSAN MOUNTAIN
1,567 M ABOVE SEA LEVEL
AT THE HEART OF BAEKDUDAEGAN
THE HOME OF VARIOUS ALPINE PLANTS
THE MOST FAMOUS SNOWY LANDSCAPE IN KOREA
AND ONE OF THE MOST POPULAR SUNRISE SPOTS
VISITED BY MANY HIKERS
DESCEND CLUB'S FIRST QUEST
WATCH THE SUNRISE FROM TAEBAEKSAN
That means we must wake up
by 5:00 a.m. at the latest.
THE HIKE IS IN TWO DAYS
-Maybe even earlier?
-Not by five.
By 6:00 or 7:00 a.m.,
-We must be up there.
-we should already be up there.
SUNRISE IS AT 7:37 A.M.
I think we should start hiking
by 5:00 a.m., at the latest.
We have both good news and bad news.
-We'll hear the bad news first.
-Bad news.
From your accommodation to Taebaeksan,
it takes about two and a half hours.
It takes so long.
Then we shouldn't sleep at all.
We calculated the time and decided
to go to bed at 8:00 p.m. tomorrow.
-What?
-We'll go to bed at 8:00 p.m.
What time do we wake up?
-At 2:00 a.m.
-What?
WAKE UP AT 2:00 A.M.!
-Okay.
-What's the good news?
The time it takes to go up and down
is very short.
Less than four hours.
4 HOURS ROUND TRIP
THAT'S GOOD NEWS?
We don't do this even when going fishing.
What's wrong with you?
LOL
BUT THERE'S A BENEFIT
We have a badge system.
Do you know how many kilometers
you walked today?
About 12 km?
A round trip of 17 km.
A ROUND TRIP OF 17 KM
According to the kilometers you walk,
we'll give you kilometer badges.
THEY GOT 17 KM FROM THE SEORAKSAN HIKE
Then does that lead to… this?
I wonder what.
Maybe a bonus.
Something like prize money.
So you want money?
Of course. You don't like it?
I want to be on Three Meals a Day.
IT'S BETTER THAN THAT
If you reach 50 km,
you'll get 11.25 g of gold.
And if you reach 100 km,
you'll get a gold badge and a prize.
The right to change the theme
of our show as you like.
SHOW CHANGE PRIVILEGES
Hey, instead of Taebaeksan,
let's hike Seoraksan four more times.
INTRIGUED
If you reach 100 km,
you can discuss among yourselves,
and if you decide that hiking
is not right for you, you can quit it
and change the theme.
SENSATIONAL OFFER
You'll have that right.
Avatar Blind Date is fun. Want to do it?
HIS CONTENT ON YOUTUBE
We can just sit
and give instructions
via a radio. It's so fun.
PLUGGING HIS OWN CONTENT
Honestly, I really enjoyed it.
Right? It's really fun.
Hey, but 100 km is…
To reach 100 km,
we have to hike like today
five or six more times.
Right…
THEY END THE MEAL FEELING DOWN
MOVING TO THEIR ACCOMMODATION BY BUS
TAKE A HIKE!
My legs…
My legs hurt so much.
Oh, God.
Geez.
GRUNTS
Gosh, the stairs.
Gosh, climbing the bus stairs
felt like hiking.
HEADING TO THEIR ACCOMMODATION
WHILE GROANING
Seriously.
I respect the directors so much.
I mean it. Geez.
They're so cool.
After all that, they're still filming.
Seriously, I…
I can't complain in front of them.
I mean, I already did, but…
My closest friend these days
is a camera director.
Whenever he works abroad,
he goes running all the time.
I thought, "What a good job he has."
But I changed my mind today.
All the camera directors
across the country,
you have my respect.
Will you shower and go to bed right away?
Maybe we should eat something?
My blood sugar's low, so I think I'll have
some sweet cake, fruit, or snacks
before going to bed.
PASSED OUT
SNORING
AFTER 30 MINUTES OF SNORING
GOSEONG-GUN
TOSEONG-MYEON
THEY ARRIVE AT THEIR ACCOMMODATION
We're here.
You guys snored like…
Like crazy, right?
-I thought it was a dream. Was it real?
-They snored like…
I thought I was dreaming.
GROANING
BARELY CLIMBING DOWN THE BUS
Wow…
-It's nice.
-What a nice house.
We're staying at such a nice place?
DESCEND CLUB'S FIRST BASE CAMP
SEORAKSAN
ACCOMMODATION
RIGHT IN FRONT OF BLUE GOSEONG SEA
IT WILL WASH AWAY THE FATIGUE
FROM THE TOUGH HIKE
What is this place?
Why is it so nice?
THEIR FIRST COZY SPACE
I'll sleep on the couch right away.
There are two beds.
THE SPACE THEY'LL REST IN
BIG BEDROOM
SMALL BEDROOM
What? We can all sleep here.
VERY SATISFIED
This is so nice.
I want to sleep there.
ARGUING OVER THE ROOMS
They'll be uncomfortable.
Why don't you use that room?
I'll feel more comfortable
in the living room.
You know, I really…
My snoring is really terrible.
VOLUNTEERS TO SLEEP IN THE LIVING ROOM
BIG BEDROOM
CHAE-MIN & TARZZAN
SMALL BEDROOM
DOWOON
-The convenience store's right outside.
-Right.
THEY HEAD TO THE CONVENIENCE STORE
FOR SNACKS
When we left after the barbecue,
it was so cold
that I can still remember it.
What was the shelter called again?
Huiun…
No, Huimun?
What was it?
-What was it?
-Huimun… Hui…
IT'S AT THE TIP OF THEIR TONGUE
Hui…
Huijeong?
-Huijeonggak!
-Is it?
"Huijeonggak" sounds like
some very nice Chinese restaurant.
What was it?
Was it Hoichungwon? What was it?
Hoichungwon Observatory?
Hui… Huijungdae?
I think it was something like that.
You'll see when it's aired.
…THE FORGOTTEN HUIUNGAK SHELTER
-Hello.
Sweets are here.
And we need snacks for tomorrow.
Green grape candy's the best.
Then should we buy this?
Yes, we can all share this one.
Let's do that.
BUYING SNACKS FOR TAEBAEKSAN
And one more for tomorrow…
The day after tomorrow, right?
Oh, you're right.
My heart almost sank.
GIVEN ONE MORE DAY TO LIVE
Now, let's buy what we'll eat now.
I've felt hungry all day today.
CONSTANTLY FEELING HUNGRY
What should we eat?
Wow, there's ice cream.
Should we buy it too?
Gosh, ice cream…
Vanilla flavor…
CAN'T RESIST SWEET TREATS
And I crave…
CHECKING OUT THE BREAD SECTION
Having this with milk is so good.
You know, right?
Be honest.
-Is that good for you?
-Come on.
You're the most enthusiastic
I've seen today.
It'll be so good.
I'll pay and send you the amount later.
Let's go Dutch.
MANAGER CAR PAYS WITHOUT HESITATION
It feels like we're on a trip.
What's the theme of the show?
Our show?
It's about hiking.
Do you like hiking?
No.
-See?
-We don't either.
We went hiking in Seoraksan
in this weather.
That's not right.
-See?
-Did you hear that? It's crazy.
HE'S ON THEIR SIDE
Have you watched 2 Days & 1 Night?
Yes.
The one who produced that show
is the producer of this show.
Mr. Nah Yung-suk.
Yes, that Mr. Nah.
made us hike Seoraksan
in this cold weather.
FIRST PERSON SYMPATHIZING WITH HIM
In 2 Days & 1 Night, they go into water.
But you didn't do that, did you?
EVERYONE: SILENT
Then they're going easy on you.
-Thank you.
-Bye.
I think we can eat here.
Yes, let's eat here.
A MODEST SNACK PARTY
I feel so happy just being inside a house.
NOTICING
LAUGHING
He keeps spacing out.
Is it good?
I'm so tired.
I expected it,
but it was harder than I thought.
It felt like a battle of mental strength
at the end.
It felt so frustrating
when it was almost over.
That was when the battle began.
For me, it was better
when we were climbing up
-than the last part.
-Right.
Watching for rocks and being careful,
it was somewhat fun.
After that, I started to loosen up
and was like, "When does it end?"
Even after we saw the Buddha statue,
it was a long way to go.
Right, I was so shocked.
Seriously, I thought we'd reach
the parking lot soon.
But it wasn't there.
Seriously.
COMING BACK DOWN FELT NEVER-ENDING
If you get an offer for a hiking movie,
what will you do?
Seoraksan?
The title is "Seoraksan."
A SUDDEN "WHAT IF" GAME
And you have a feeling it'll hit big.
But you have to hike it like today,
eight more times to film it.
And since you're a rescue worker,
you have to carry people for real.
HE THOROUGHLY EXPLAINS THE DETAILS
I should do it.
-Wow.
-Gosh, so professional.
-He's professional.
-Right.
CRUNCHING
Should we go to bed?
Yes, let's go to bed.
I'll sleep on the floor.
No, I will.
No, no.
LATE-NIGHT BED BATTLE
I think I'll wake up first, so…
No.
-What?
-No, you can't.
-Why not?
-I…
BOTH TRY TO TAKE THE FLOOR
No, please. You can't.
-Rock-paper-scissors, then?
-Okay.
Winner takes what?
Winner takes…
-the floor.
-Okay.
-Rock-paper-scissors.
-Scissors.
ROCK
WIN
LOSE
TARZZAN SLEEPS ON THE FLOOR
Good night, guys.
-Good night.
SEORAKSAN TRAINING ENDS
MORNING COMES
TODAY IS A RECOVERY DAY
CURRENT TIME
CHAE-MIN WAKES UP AFTER 12 HOURS OF SLEEP
TARZZAN WAKES UP TOO
RECOVERY STEP 1
ENOUGH SLEEP
Geez!
Did you sleep well?
I passed out.
STROKING
THEY'VE GROWN A LOT CLOSER
-How are you feeling?
-Feeling good.
-Good.
-And you?
I'm feeling great.
-I'm recovered.
-You're young indeed.
Are they still sleeping?
I think so.
Should we go to the first floor
and eat cereal?
FEELING HUNGRY UPON WAKING UP
What?
I woke up way earlier.
Hey.
What? Were you not sleeping?
I went to bed early, you know.
-When did you wake up?
-Around 8:00 a.m.
Really?
You were the first to wake up.
I even went downstairs and had ramyeon.
What?
What? You already ate?
2 HOURS AGO
HE FINISHED A BOWL OF RAMYEON
Wow, and here we thought
we were the early birds.
He must be still sleeping, right?
Right.
DOWOON IS STILL ASLEEP
"A Book for Hikers to Read on Mountains."
RECOVERY STEP 2
MINDSET TRAINING
"Wrong hiking"?
WRONG HIKING HARMS YOUR HEALTH
That's terrible. A book to read…
20 HIKING HABIT CHECKS
"I go hiking for exercise
even though I'm tired from overworking."
It's wrong.
Isn't that us tomorrow?
I think we'll be hiking wrong.
"I often feel dead on my feet."
This is too tough.
Careful.
Are you okay?
"I sweat profusely when hiking."
You suddenly look ill.
You look pale.
"My knees hurt while climbing down."
My thighs feel tight already.
Gosh, this is…
"After hiking,
I feel completely exhausted."
If at least seven are applicable to you,
it means hiking
is harming your health.
Gosh, it was really tough yesterday.
22 HOURS
BEFORE THE SUNRISE FROM TAEBAEKSAN
KITCHEN, 1ST FLOOR
-Are you going to have eggs?
-I should.
We need protein.
I'm thinking of making French toast,
since we have eggs.
BREAKFAST IS FRENCH TOAST
WASHING HANDS FIRST
I'm frying eggs in butter,
and it smells so good.
Do you like your eggs sunny side up?
Totally.
A SIDE DISH OF FRIED EGGS, COMPLETE
BEATING THE EGGS THOROUGHLY
Just soak them with your hand.
BOLD MOVE
It looks good.
Right?
CUTTING BANANA IN THE MEANTIME
WASHES STRAWBERRIES
AND PUTS THEM ON THE BANANA SLICES
BRUNCH COMPLETE
Look at us two guys…
CHORTLES
…having brunch.
Wow, this is…
We have to take a photo.
This is my first time.
PROUD
CHAE-MIN AND TARZZAN'S
PETIT BRUNCH
-Thank you for the food.
There are a lot of eggs.
It should be more, actually.
-Really?
-Yes.
How many eggs do you usually eat?
I try to eat 30 g of protein per meal.
But there's some egg in the toast too.
Right.
Hey, my dear friends.
I picked up some coffee for you.
-Thank you.
CARRYING CAREFULLY
BUT SPILLING SOME
Hey, do you want to have some?
No, I'm good. I'm full.
When do you think Dowoon will wake up?
At 4:00 p.m.?
I bet he'll wake up so late.
I think he'll wake up…
around 1:00 or 2:00 p.m.?
CURRENT TIME
HE DOESN'T LOOK LIKE HE'LL WAKE UP AT ALL
I wish tomorrow
would be relaxing like this.
RECOVERY STEP 3
PROTEIN INTAKE
Yes.
CHAE-MIN TAKES A CALL AFTER THE MEAL
Yes, we hiked Seoraksan yesterday.
It wasn't easy at all.
I think I just kept climbing up
without talking.
No, it was so tough that I couldn't talk.
So I passed out around 10:00 p.m.
Who is it?
It's my mother.
It'll be too heartbreaking
for her to watch.
No. He says it'll be too heartbreaking
for you to watch.
ONE HIKE, INSTANT BAD SON
The show title is Take a Hike!
and it's about
finding out why we go hiking.
CONCEPT: FINDING OUT WHY PEOPLE HIKE
But I don't think we'll find out.
I think mountains are most beautiful
when we see them from afar.
Okay.
HE FEELS BETTER THANKS TO MOM
I love you.
Sit here.
Who did you pick as the MVP?
What about you?
Car, of course.
-Why me?
-Me too.
I said I was proud of you.
That's good.
-I said you complained less than expected.
-"I was so proud of him."
WHY HE'S MVP:
COMPLAINED LESS THAN EXPECTED
Who do you think the MVP is?
Car, the garden.
Since he complained
less than I'd expected.
It was so tough for him,
but he finished it, and I think
that's what matters the most.
I'm younger than him,
but I was proud of him.
Today's MVP
is you, Car, the garden.
TWO-TIME SEORAKSAN MVP
I just put that on.
You did?
SLUGGISH
It's so dry.
-What? You woke up.
-What?
DOWOON WAKES UP
You should wash up now.
-Foam rollers.
-Hey, how are your legs?
DOWOON GRABS A FOAM ROLLER FIRST
Dowoon, put these on.
-What are those?
-For your calves.
AN ITEM TARZZAN RECOMMENDS: YOGA RINGS
On your calves, like this.
-Slide it up to the calf.
-All the way.
Actually, you need to walk with them on
to get better.
Wait, walk like this?
Seriously?
HE LOOKS LIKE A TODDLER LEARNING TO WALK
Come on, hurry up.
THEY ARE GOOD FRIENDS HELPING HIM WALK
-Hey, you woke up.
-Yes.
When did you wake up?
-Like this?
-Yes, like that.
-Yes, but that looks painful.
Wow, this feels nice too.
INTERESTED
GROANS
Like this?
JUST GOING FOR IT
Yes, up and down.
UP AND DOWN
Feels nice, right?
Side rolling is the best, though.
-Like this?
-Yes.
Like that.
GROANS
Side rolling's so painful.
So that's how you do it.
-Do some more.
-I think you need it,
-or you'll cramp up tomorrow.
-Exactly.
FOAM ROLLER
FOAM PILLOW
Isn't this what it's really for?
-I need to do it too.
-Small ones are more painful.
GROANS
It's really painful.
Geez.
It pisses me off that they prepared them.
They set them all up
because they knew we'd have sore muscles.
THE STAFF'S FORESIGHT ANGERS HIM
RECOVERY STEP 4
MUSCLE RECOVERY COMPLETE
CURRENT TIME
-Car.
-Yes?
How about we go have some crabs today?
Sure, let's do that.
Wow, the wind's so strong.
-Who should drive?
-I'll do it.
-Why's it so strong?
-It's pushing me.
It's like a disaster movie.
-It makes me walk fast.
-I'll ride shotgun.
-Okay, I'll drive.
-Okay.
It's so cold.
THEY MANAGE TO GET IN
Hold on. The door won't close.
It's unbelievable.
-Seat belts.
-Seat belts, everyone.
It's so cold.
Hey, just go.
FRANTIC
Open it just a little.
We'll go ahead of you. You might run off.
Why didn't you move faster then?
That was close.
Do they really suspect we might run off?
I bet, because of me.
HIGHLY LIKELY TO RUN OFF
Next time he comes, pretend to stop
and go a little further.
HEADING OUT WITH THE ESCAPE TIP
ACCOMMODATION
RESTAURANT
I feel comfortable around you guys now.
I do, too.
It isn't easy
to become comfortable like this.
Honestly, even if we go around
only in our underwear in our room,
I don't think it'll feel awkward.
-I slept in only my underwear.
-Really?
I saw it.
-For real?
-They were black.
You're right.
During our first meeting, you said
we'd get really close
after our first hike.
It was quite awkward
even to call them by their names.
But we became like close friends quickly.
I'm not the type
to be on a first-name basis quickly.
But maybe because of the hike,
I could easily call Chae-min by his name.
I think some kind
of comradeship was forged.
That's very important, you know?
The sea in Goseong is really clear.
I came to the beach here last summer.
It wasn't crowded,
and the water was so clear.
Oh, the sea?
I heard the East Sea is beautiful.
BEACH, MOUNTAINS, LAKE
GOSEONG, WHERE SEA, LAKE,
AND MOUNTAINS MEET
I just saw mountains. It's pissing me off.
Sorry, I'll go fast.
Mountains over there…
VROOM
Are you flooring it?
Yes.
It sounds like Mario Kart.
WHILE FLOORING IT
THEY ARRIVE AT DONGMYEONG PORT IN SOKCHO
Oh, there's a lot here. Good choice.
-I think.
-Right.
THE CRAB RESTAURANT
CHAE-MIN AND TARZZAN FOUND
Hello.
You can keep your shoes on.
Goodness.
What should we have?
-King crab?
-Sure, let's do that.
Then, a four-person set of king crab.
Good.
I'm hungry now that I'm here.
-Right.
-Suddenly…
Gosh, I'm in trouble.
Look at the crab mustard.
KING CRAB
-This is bad.
-Thank you for the food.
Look at the meat.
-It's so plump.
-Wow.
Let's dig in.
-This was a good choice.
-Right.
The king crab meat is so…
This is my first time.
You should dip it into this.
Oh, really?
It's better this way.
CRAB MEAT + INNARDS
The crab mustard.
AS TARZZAN RECOMMENDED
-It's so savory.
-It's amazing, gosh.
What is this? Innards?
I think you can just eat it.
It's also meat.
It's good, wow.
It looks like a crab stick.
BUT IT'S REAL CRAB MEAT
We're eating every meal so passionately.
Right.
We should eat well.
-Is that rice?
-Yes.
Thank you.
FOR THE PASSIONATE EATERS
-Thank you.
It looks great.
Seriously.
CRAB MUSTARD FRIED RICE
This is so good too.
Is it good?
It's so good with kimchi.
It's so good.
It really is.
Instead of wanting to go hiking
while watching our show,
viewers will want to eat the food we eat.
You can eat the noodles
if you like them al dente.
Thank you.
RED SNOW CRAB RAMYEON
It looks good. It looks perfect now.
I can smell crab.
Is it different?
It tastes like the sea, I'd say.
Wow, it is different.
I can taste the crab flavor.
My God, the broth is…
It's so good.
IT MAKES HIM KEEP EXCLAIMING
It feels like we're besties already.
We are, since we ate crab together.
You're crab-solutely right.
While filming a hiking show,
I thought I'd lose a lot of weight.
-But we're eating so well.
-You're right.
If you make good choices
on food like this, we're happy too.
THE CREW IS HAPPY TOO
-That feels more rewarding.
-Since we can eat it too.
Right, because the staff
have to eat what we eat?
I think we should think about this.
But if we keep it up,
they might be more accepting
when we ask something.
Is that so?
We can make a deal.
Give and take?
They might lower the difficulty.
They might feel bad.
That's good.
You're quite the diplomat.
I tend to do things unilaterally.
We should appoint Chae-min
as our diplomat.
DESCEND CLUB'S DIPLOMAT
Does a hiking club need a diplomat?
It's important.
When we need to negotiate with them,
your diplomatic attitude…
ESSENTIAL DIPLOMACY SKILLS
…will be very crucial. And as for Dowoon…
Appoint him as our driver?
Just "driver" sounds lame.
Let's give him a proper title.
-How about the Minister of Transport?
-Minister of Transport.
MINISTER OF TRANSPORT
Foreign Affairs and Transport.
Sounds good.
And I'm the Prime Minister.
Then he's the President.
PRESIDENT TAR
It seems Producer Nah's determined
to put us through a lot,
but I'm anxious
because we're eating so well.
I mean, he's known for not giving food
and not letting members sleep.
Wait.
If we say things like that,
he might change his mind
and do something like that.
PREVENTING A DIPLOMATIC CRISIS
We made it clear.
If we can't sleep or eat,
we can't do this.
He's diplomatic indeed.
He sure keeps a balance between us.
He's like Zhuge Liang.
Zhuge Liang?
CHAE LIANG
What are you, then?
I'm just a fat man.
A fat man.
FAT ZHANG FEI
But Jung-won is right about that.
I think it's our first time
letting members sleep and eat well.
But not giving us food after hiking?
That would be so…
I think it's because
we all hiked together.
If they didn't,
it might've been different.
Since we did it together?
KEEN INSIGHT
Since we all need to eat.
Anyway, it's so nice
that you all have titles.
I've been wondering what kind of quest
there could be in the mountains.
What about after the sunrise?
Let's talk about the next one
after the Taebaeksan quest is over.
No.
"No."
I'd like to go somewhere
I haven't been to.
It's okay as long as it's "san."
"San" Francisco.
That place is really nice.
-It is.
-It's really nice and warm.
Then how about we go to Bu"san" next?
Busan is a really good "san."
When we go to Busan, I'll book a KTX.
A BOLD PLEDGE
That's good.
Hey, there are a lot of stairs
in the KTX station.
The Korail…
It's really tiring.
The stairs in Seoul Station are so steep.
Actually, Ansan is also good.
It's nice and close.
My hometown, Ilsan, is good too.
Ilsan? That's a great "san" too.
Ilsan's nice.
We can have good kalguksu there.
ILSAN'S FAMOUS KALGUKSU TRAIL
It's good for the directors too.
They can borrow their equipment there.
THERE ARE BROADCAST STATIONS
There are a few broadcast stations there.
There's Yongsan too.
Yongsan is the best. Seriously.
What was that yesterday?
-Biseondae?
-Yes.
If Seoraksan has Biseondae,
it has Soonchunhyang-dae.
Near Soonchunhyang University Hospital,
we can have our snacks
at Hannam Intersection.
There are many shelters too.
Yes, there are a lot there.
It's filled with shelters.
THEBLACKLABEL shelter's there.
TARZZAN'S RECORD LABEL
That's a great place.
Yeah, it's good.
Directors, can you each
recommend a mountain?
-Since you all experienced Seoraksan…
-No. Don't.
-Director.
I think he and I are on the same page.
Yongsan, right?
DIRECTOR HONG JEONG-PYO
Because we're on the same team.
-Yes, he and I are on the same team.
-Right.
-Those hiking with equipment are
-Yes.
-on the same team as us.
-No.
-That director likes hiking.
-Yes.
-We should avoid him.
-Oh, I see.
CAMERA DIRECTOR HONG DEOK-HWAN
As for him…
He seems to have a lot to say.
I'm sure he's on our side.
AUDIO DIRECTOR KIM SEON-U
I saw the look on his face.
As our diplomat,
why don't you talk to them in private?
-I think I can persuade them easily.
-Okay.
Quite easily.
He's Hong Jeong-pyo, the main director.
He's also the main director
of Culinary Class Wars.
Hey, he directed Culinary Class Wars,
and now a hiking show?
Absurd.
From filming food…
HE'S FILMING BEAUTIFUL MOUNTAINS INSTEAD
Maybe he was duped just like us?
Isn't it possible?
REASONABLE DOUBT
It is possible.
-I'll drive on our way back.
-Okay.
RECOVERY STEP 5
MORE PROTEIN INTAKE
Today's schedule is all about eating.
You're right.
We hiked all day long yesterday,
and we're eating all day long today.
It's like the National Training Center.
We're training too.
It does feel like training.
Exactly.
I think we'll be really motivated
if we do that.
-What?
-Paid money per certain meters.
If we do that,
even Jung-won will never give up.
-It's good.
-You know, how about this?
You know the taximeter, right?
-Yes.
-Sounds good.
What if each of us wears that
while hiking?
PROPOSAL: HIKING WITH BODY TRACKERS
I don't think
I'll feel good about it though.
Earning money
according to how much we suffer…
But if we use a pedometer,
it'd be 10,000 won per 10,000 steps.
That's infuriating.
Then if we walk 30,000 steps,
it's only 30,000 won.
But even in a taximeter,
there's a basic fare.
PLOTTING WAYS TO CASH IN ON HIKING
Good job today.
-Good job.
-You too.
ARRIVING AT THE HOUSE
-Hey, this is…
-This is nice.
It feels like home.
-Yes, I wanted to come back quickly.
-And it's just been a day.
It does feel like home.
WHILE THEY ARE REUNITED WITH THEIR ROOMS
FLOWING WIND
FLOWING WAVES
FLYING PLASTIC BAG
AND…
14 HOURS 25 MINUTES
UNTIL SUNRISE
STRETCHING WITH FOAM ROLLERS
13 HOURS 10 MINUTES
UNTIL SUNRISE
WATCHING CAR, THE GARDEN'S YOUTUBE CHANNEL
12 HOURS
UNTIL SUNRISE
WATCHING DAY6'S PERFORMANCE
11 HOURS 22 MINUTES
UNTIL SUNRISE
DINNER
10 HOURS 57 MINUTES
UNTIL SUNRISE
ROCK-PAPER-SCISSORS FOR DISHWASHING
DOWOON LOSES
DISHWASHER
10 HOURS 37 MINUTES
UNTIL SUNRISE
EVERYONE IS GATHERED IN THE DINING ROOM
EXCEPT FOR DOWOON
SCRIBBLING
The descent…
-Schedule?
-The Descend Club.
No, let's schedule our descent,
since that's our goal.
PLANNING THEIR HIKE
-Right.
-Our goal isn't reaching the summit.
I sent you a trail.
-You did?
-Yes.
I wonder what kind of lovely trail it is.
It's the National Park homepage.
It's called the Yuilsa Trail.
TAEBAEKSAN
YUILSA TRAIL
It begins from the Yuilsa Parking Lot.
THE SHORT YET TOUGH 2-HOUR TRAIL
A BRUTAL SNOWY CLIMB
AT THE END OF THE ENDLESS RIDGES
IS THE FINAL DESTINATION, JANGGUNBONG PEAK
THEY MUST ARRIVE HERE BEFORE SUNRISE
SUCKS TEETH
ChatGPT says that the trail is not bad.
CONFIRMATION COMPLETE
This is the clock.
It's cute.
Didn't I draw it well?
It's quite detailed, you know.
DESCEND CLUB
Oh, it's good.
-So there are four?
-Yes, us four.
CHECKING DETAILS
SCHEDULING BEGINS
When is sunrise?
SUNRISE TIME
Enter the mountain.
ENTER THE MOUNTAIN
By 5:30 a.m.
SUNRISE
The weather is crucial.
-Right.
-All right.
We wake up at 2:00 a.m.
WAKE UP
Scheduling's done, then.
Good.
JUST HAPPY THAT IT'S DONE
Are you doodling?
I just drew
how we'll move to the mountain.
I like drawing, so…
-Draw more, then.
-Yes.
-I drew one for each.
-This one too.
The sunrise.
That's our quest.
MEANWHILE, DOWOON IS DOING THE DISHES
DISHWASHER
STILL PLANNING
-Our plan is…
-Yes.
We might get cold while we rest.
-So taking short breaks often…
-Often?
would be better.
Even with a one-minute break,
you recover a little.
SUGGESTING AN EFFICIENT STRATEGY
Since it's so early in the morning,
we don't know how our condition will be.
So,
if any of us gets tired,
we'll honestly say, "I need a break."
We'll take a break then.
TAKE FREQUENT SHORT BREAKS
WHEN ANYONE WANTS
-Like this?
-Yes.
If we feel tired, just stop.
That's our rule.
Right, that's how
I finished it eventually.
Though I wasn't
intentionally taking breaks.
-Still, you got better.
-Right.
Will Dowoon be taking the lead?
-No, Tarzzan will.
-Tarzzan? Okay.
Slow one, fast one, slow one, fast one.
And the directors will be in the middle.
FORMATION RULE DURING HIKE
TARZZAN LEADS, ROTATING PACE
That's our rule.
How long will we stay on the top?
Assuming we reach it.
Is there a shelter on the summit?
No.
Then, since there's no shelter there,
let's climb down when we feel cold.
-Okay, right away.
-We must move when we're cold.
IF IT GETS COLD,
HEAD DOWN WITHOUT LOOKING BACK
"Wait. We need to take a picture here."
We won't.
We won't care. We'll descend.
Good.
DESCEND CLUB'S MEETING ENDS
Hold on. Guys.
-Dowoon, listen.
-No, hold on a second.
There's a dishwasher here.
Why didn't anyone tell me?
There is?
But while you did that, we made a plan.
Yes, check it out.
-Just follow our plan.
-Okay.
DOWOON'S VILLAIN ARC
This is a plan
for descending and going home early.
Okay.
HISTORIC FIRST PLAN
It's our club's first-ever plan.
-I'll explain.
-Okay.
We wake up at 2:00 a.m.
-Since we must head out by 2:30 a.m.
-Okay.
And it'll be cold, so we'll climb down
right after watching the sunrise.
Right after…
-the sunrise.
-Okay.
As soon as we see the sun.
LEARNING FAST
Be like this.
READY
Like Usain Bolt.
As soon as we see it.
IMMEDIATELY SWITCHING TO TRAIL RUNNING
What about a penalty? Let's set a rule.
Let's set a rule and a fine.
If we say certain things…
-We can't say something negative.
-Okay.
-Nothing negative.
-Let's stay positive tomorrow.
-How much should the fine be?
-The fine?
Let's make it big. 100,000 won.
But I think we need a limit.
If you have to pay 100,000 won
whenever you say something negative,
I think once our show is over,
Car-the might have to sell his car.
THEN HE BECOMES JUST "THE GARDEN"
So negative.
So how about we pay a fine just once?
I mean, you just need to
pay a 100,000-won fine per one hike.
I think that's better.
Well…
Should we raise the fine?
-The fine…
-Raise it.
-It's per hike.
-Right.
-Make it 300,000 won.
-Good.
DESCEND CLUB'S
FIRST HIKING PLAN COMPLETED
He and I are going to sleep
in hiking clothes.
LAUGHING
You do that when you go to the ski resort
so you can leave right away.
BEDTIME APPROACHES
That's a good idea.
AND THE NIGHT DEEPENS
I don't want to go hiking tomorrow.
THEY DON'T WANT TO GO TO BED
I want to wake up at 8:00 a.m.
It's nice to chat with people
speaking the same language.
-It is.
-Right.
My ways to relieve stress
-are things like basketball and gym.
-Right.
TOPIC 1: HOW TO RELIEVE STRESS
And finding your own ways to do that
is the smart thing to do.
-Right.
-Wow, you're incredible.
Since I wanted to perform on stage,
I needed to learn how to dance.
TOPIC 2: DREAMS AND JOBS
So I started modern dance.
Now that I've talked with you guys
since we started filming,
I'm glad I decided to do this.
There are many things I can't do
since I'm timid.
TOPIC 3: EMOTIONAL CONFESSIONS
So people around me were surprised.
NOSTALGIC GAMES
AND NOSTALGIC DRAMA SHOWS
TIME HAS FLOWN
YAWNING
Now, let's go to bed.
Let's try to sleep.
What time is it?
It's 12:00 a.m. now?
ONLY 2 HOURS LEFT UNTIL WAKE-UP TIME
THEY GO TO BED FOR REAL
TIME PASSES BY FAST
CURRENT TIME
We need to get up.
-What?
-We need to get up.
It's 2:00 a.m.
You woke up at 2:00 a.m., right?
How was it?
Well, it was hard.
Because of a drama filming schedule,
the earliest I had to wake up
was 2:30 a.m.
And I broke the record this time.
Well…
Thank you.
CHAE-MIN GETS UP
CAR, THE GARDEN GETS UP
Dowoon.
Yes?
-Oh, you didn't sleep?
-No.
Did you?
-A little.
-Wow.
DOWOON COULDN'T SLEEP A WINK
Gosh, will we be able to hike?
Seriously.
We'll have to.
It feels like a moment ago.
LASTLY, TARZZAN
EVERYONE IS UP
NONE OF THEM SLEPT PROPERLY
I'm mad already.
SAYING SOMETHING NICE RIGHT AWAY
-I'm pissed off.
-It felt like just a nap.
BUT HE GETS CHANGED THE FASTEST
WHAT DO YOU THINK YOUR WEAKNESS IS?
I'M IMPATIENT
TARZZAN WEARS AN ORANGE BALACLAVA
You're bundled up today.
Yes.
Apparently, it's so windy.
WIND SPEED IN TAEBAEKSAN
"A LITTLE STRONG" TO "STRONG"
IT'S GOING TO FEEL STRONGER
BECAUSE OF THE OPEN RIDGES
SPACING OUT
TRYING TO WAKE UP
WHILE FOLDING UP THE BEDDING
UPON WAKING UP, HE TAKES SUPPLEMENTS
AND SOME MORE
HABIT FOR STAMINA
TAKING JUICE AND SUPPLEMENTS
QUICKLY NOURISHING HIS SKIN AS WELL
Do we need this?
Yes, we should wear them from the start.
GAITERS PROTECT LEGS FROM THE COLD
AND PREVENT SNOW FROM GETTING IN
ALL READY
Let's go down.
You didn't forget anything?
IT'S ONLY BEEN 34 HOURS SINCE SEORAKSAN
Feels good.
THEY DIDN'T GET MUCH SLEEP
WITH ALL KINDS OF UNFAVORABLE CONDITIONS
GETTING ON THE BUS
Geez.
HEADING FOR TAEBAEKSAN
We'll turn the lights off.
-Okay.
DRIVING NONSTOP
ACCOMMODATION
TAEBAEKSAN
THEY'RE HEADED TO…
DANGUN SHRINE
A HOLY MOUNTAIN
WITH A LONG HISTORY
TRUE TO ITS NAME,
MEANING "BIG, BRIGHT MOUNTAIN,"
THE SUN RISES
OVER THE EAST SEA HORIZON,
ILLUMINATING THE DAZZLING SNOWY LANDSCAPE
TAEBAEKSAN
THE MOST BEAUTIFUL MOUNTAIN
FOR WINTER HIKING
260-68 HYEOL-DONG, TAEBAEK CITY
YUILSA PARKING LOT
We're here.
ARRIVING AT THE PARKING LOT
TWO ARE GETTING READY, HALF AWAKE
AND THESE TWO ARE STILL HALF ASLEEP
WHAT AWAITS THEM IS
DARKNESS
COVERED IN SNOW FROM YESTERDAY
NUMBER 1 CAUSE OF FATAL ACCIDENTS:
HEART ATTACK
FOR WINTER HIKING,
CRAMPONS ARE A MUST, NOT A CHOICE
GETTING OFF THE BUS
It was my first time hiking in the dark,
so I was quite nervous.
I mean,
I was nervous that I might feel so scared.
Because of my usual tight schedule,
I sometimes don't get enough sleep,
so that was okay.
But that was for performing on stage,
not for going hiking.
It was an unusual experience.
Geez.
It's so cold.
HEADLAMP
HEADLAMP ON
PUTTING ON CRAMPONS BY HEADLAMP LIGHT
Darn it.
2ND TRY
His legs are slim
compared to his upper body.
And he knows that.
I think he should work out his legs.
WEAK LEGS
You can lean on the bus.
THE MANAGER LISTENS TO THE PRESIDENT
It's upside down.
Is this good enough?
STILL NOT USED TO CRAMPONS
CONDUCTED UNDER THE SUPERVISION
OF PROFESSIONALS
The wind will be cold,
so keep your gloves on.
Okay.
CRAMPONS ARE ON
Who will take the lead?
Tarzzan will today.
TARZZAN TAKES THE LEAD AS PLANNED
Gosh, it's cold.
-We have good news.
-Okay.
The apparent temperature is just -19°C.
You know, it was -27°C in Seoraksan.
I saw the Taebaeksan CCTV feed.
And it's so windy on the summit.
WIND IS VERY STRONG ON THE SUMMIT
THE HIKING TRAILS ARE SNOWY AND DARK
WITH THE FATIGUE
FROM THE SEORAKSAN HIKE TWO DAYS AGO
DESPITE THE UNFAVORABLE CONDITIONS,
TODAY'S QUEST IS…
WATCHING THE SUNRISE FROM TAEBAEKSAN
SUNRISE TIME
2 HOURS TO THE TOP
WILL THEY BE ABLE TO WATCH THE SUNRISE?
Let's go!
THEY START HIKING
9 MINUTES LATER THAN PLANNED
My lower body feels colder.
Right. My legs feel cold here.
You're right.
THEY BEGIN WITH COLD LEGS
TODAY'S COURSE: YUILSA TRAIL
YUILSA TRAIL ENTRANCE
Gosh, this is…
My hands feel cold.
COLD SPREADS TO THE UPPER BODY
I should put on gloves.
-Give me the poles.
-What?
-These.
-Oh, thanks.
I should wear one more pair.
CHAE-MIN PUTS ON ONE MORE PAIR OF GLOVES
TARZZAN TAKES THE LEAD
AS THEY PLANNED LAST NIGHT
Wow, my hands are freezing.
DOWOON WAITS FOR CHAE-MIN
SECOND PAIR OF GLOVES ON
The tips of my fingers feel so cold today.
I've got some heat packs.
Okay.
I'll give you some later.
MASSIVE CLOUDS OF BREATH
God, my hands are freezing.
My hands are so cold.
IN COLD WEATHER
THE TIPS OF THE BODY GET COLD FIRST
SO LAYER UP AND MOVE A LOT
It's not easy from the start here.
Right.
I should keep my own pace.
There's no warm-up part.
Right.
Turning on the headlamp
and putting on the crampons
was no problem.
But I was flustered
that it was uphill from the start.
IN TODAY'S COURSE, FROM THE START
IT IS VERY STEEP
THE STEEP TRAIL CONTINUES
FOR ABOUT 20 MORE MINUTES
At first,
it felt too much for me,
since I wasn't really awake, but…
Hey, the mountain's nice, right?
SILENCE
Wow.
Wow, it's nice!
DESCEND CLUB RULES
NEGATIVE COMMENT: 300,000-WON FINE
The mountain's so…
The scenery is so beautiful.
TARZZAN'S POINT OF VIEW
BEAUTIFUL SCENERY
Is this pace okay?
Yes.
APPARENTLY, THE MOOD IS BRIGHTER
PRESIDENT TAR MAINTAINS PACE
I'm already not cold anymore
after walking a bit.
Really? That's good.
Yes. Thank God.
Gosh, the snow…
It's tough.
Geez, the snow…
There's a lot piled up.
TRYING TO BE POSITIVE
THE STEEP TRAIL IS COVERED IN SNOW
-The snow's deeper than I thought.
-Right.
THE DISTANCE BETWEEN TARZZAN
AND CAR, THE GARDEN IS GROWING
TARZZAN FROM CAR, THE GARDEN'S CAM
CAR, THE GARDEN
CHAE-MIN'S CAM
Tell me if you're tired.
-I'm tired.
-What?
I'm tired now.
Tell me if you want a break.
-No, not now.
-You can rest now.
There's no need to overdo it
in the beginning.
Was the fatigue from Seoraksan
the problem?
My legs were hurting.
That was the problem.
The trail was not bad,
but it was quite steep.
My legs felt tired so quickly.
THE AFTERMATH OF SEORAKSAN
-Go ahead.
-What?
You go ahead.
Let's take a break then.
We'll take a short break.
We'll take one or two-minute breaks often.
DESCEND CLUB RULES
TAKE A BREAK IF ANYONE WANTS IT
Does anyone want caramel? Caramel.
Me.
Thank you.
Jung-won.
-I'm good.
-Caramel? No?
-Is it from the convenience store?
HELPER DOWOON GIVES OUT SNACKS
Thank you.
Oh, there's someone behind us.
The producer.
PRODUCER NAH IS FOLLOWING
This is so tough.
Is it uphill all the way?
It's so tough.
I think so.
What?
TARZZAN'S POV
DESCEND CLUB RULES
NEGATIVE COMMENT: 300,000-WON FINE
It's so tough. Life is.
POSITIVE CAR, THE GARDEN CLARIFIES
-Life is.
-Life is tough. Right.
Life's tough. That's okay.
-Oh, life?
-Yes.
THE PRESIDENT LETS IT SLIDE
I got so many worries in life.
I have a lot on my mind.
If you complain today, you know
you must pay 300,000 won.
LIFE REGRETS OVER A FINE
You know, life is so tough.
We'll move now.
DESCEND CLUB RULES
BREAKS: LESS THAN 5 MINUTES
The pole is…
MOVING AGAIN
1 HOUR 38 MINUTES UNTIL SUNRISE
But still, it's better
than a stony, uphill trail.
-Way better.
-A trail like this is much better.
Let's take our time.
The caramel gives me energy.
TARZZAN MAINTAINS THE LEAD
AFTER HAVING A SWEET TREAT
AND THE ONE BEHIND HIM
THE DISTANCE HAS GROWN IN NO TIME
LOOKING BACK
Since I was taking the lead,
I felt rushed.
I felt kind of motivated
to complete the quest,
so I walked fast without realizing it,
and the distance grew.
CAR, THE GARDEN IS NEXT TO CHAE-MIN NOW
How about Tarzzan goes to the back?
-Let's keep pace with him.
-He should take the lead.
Okay, I'll take the lead.
Yes, you can take your time.
Okay.
-This is my pace. Is it okay?
-Go, go.
-Are you okay?
-I'm fine.
AS PLANNED, THE SLOW ONE TAKES THE LEAD
Everyone agreed
that Car-the should take the lead.
So he took the lead then.
All our legs haven't recovered enough yet.
Right.
-That's why it's so tough.
-Right, it seems so.
CAR-THE'S HEAVY FOOTSTEPS
Goodness…
Car-the, try using both poles
at the same time.
-That's better. Yes.
-Like this?
IT MAY BE SLOW, BUT THEY WALK TOGETHER
Hey, should we take a break
around that curve?
-Sounds good. We'll rest right above it.
-Sure.
We'll rest right above the curve.
-Okay.
"Let's take short breaks often."
That was our plan for today's hike.
But Car-the was struggling a lot.
You know, the fatigue builds up.
We could keep going
because we took breaks.
If we hiked like we did in Seoraksan,
we would've failed.
-Jung-won.
-Yes?
This chair here is not wet.
You can sit here.
No, I think it's better not to sit down.
Anyone want a drink?
I got a sports drink.
Thanks.
HERE COMES HELPER DOWOON AGAIN
I'll have a sip too.
Everyone, take a sip.
AFTER THE YOUNGEST TAKES A SIP
I also said this
when I decided to do this show.
I want to be helpful.
Honestly, I'm not good
at making others laugh.
I'm not good at making jokes
on the spot like Jung-won.
So, I tried
to look after the others, at least.
I think I found the right role for me.
By the way,
it seems your backpack is quite heavy.
-Is it?
-What did you put in?
-Just…
-Did you put in the pots?
-Yes.
-The pots?
THE SAME BACKPACK USED IN SEORAKSAN
Why don't you give them to me?
I'm not carrying much.
But the backpack isn't the problem.
Then, your legs?
Yes.
And we're not fully awake yet.
-Yes, that too.
-We're still foggy.
So foggy.
We're just walking.
If you look here,
we've come one kilometer
from Yuilsa Parking Lot,
and Cheonjedan is three kilometers away.
We're a quarter of the way, then.
-So we have 3 km to go.
-Okay.
2.7 KM LEFT UNTIL JANGGUNBONG PEAK
1 HOUR 29 MINUTES UNTIL SUNRISE
Let's go.
Okay.
We go when you go.
Right.
DESCEND CLUB RULES
BREAKS: LESS THAN 5 MINUTES
We're already a quarter of the way.
Right.
LEAD: CAR, THE GARDEN
MIDDLE 1: TARZZAN
MIDDLE 2: CHAE-MIN
TAIL: DOWOON
NOW THE PACE SEEMS PERFECT
I feel hot now.
I'm starting to feel warm now.
Right.
I should take off a layer.
-Right?
-Yes.
Jung-won, it's nothing funny, but…
Do you know Russell, a US sports brand?
-Russell?
-Russell.
I don't.
WHEN CLIMBING A SNOW MOUNTAIN,
THE LEAD PLOWS THROUGH SNOW TO MAKE A PATH
It's a hiking term.
Just go.
Russell, my foot.
I was taken aback. I got goosebumps.
Seriously.
Do you know what he said to me?
What is it?
"It's nothing funny, but…"
TELLING ON THE DOCENT
"Do you know the brand Russell?"
"Stepping on snow is called Russell."
-Stepping on snow?
-Yes.
I mean, who cares, right?
BADMOUTHING HIM SO OPENLY
I'm dumbfounded.
THANKS TO THAT, HE FEELS HOT
He's getting negative.
Gosh, this is bad.
Do you know Cha Jung-sook?
She's my aunt. Ms. Cha Jung-sook.
Hey.
Why don't we
-take a break?
-To take off a layer?
I should take off some clothes.
I'm feeling hot.
A BREAK TO TAKE OFF CLOTHES
While we're at it,
let's split what you're carrying.
Seriously, it's heavy.
No, the bag is really fine.
It's just that
my thighs were hurting earlier.
-It was really your thighs?
-Yes. I'm fine now.
But still, it's really heavy.
FEELING THE WEIGHT
I didn't even feel the backpack, no lie.
My thighs hurt so annoyingly earlier.
They still hurt?
It was so steep from the start.
-It was.
-True.
I'm fine now.
Wow, so positive.
You guys are not tired?
I am.
-Right?
-Yes.
I'm not the only one, right?
-Apparently, it'll get better.
-What?
A POSITIVE MAN
A "NAH"GATIVE MAN
It felt like climbing a ski slope.
ALL READY
You got changed.
You look like a spaceman.
Right?
SPACEMAN PERFORMANCE
It looks like you're on the moon.
Wow, you can do those moves.
Did you know you can change the color?
A HEADLAMP PERFORMANCE
It changed with a button.
-Hey, Tarzzan.
-Yes?
Don't enjoy hiking too much.
-Wait.
-You're enjoying it too much.
That's not right for our club.
You're enjoying it too much.
Take it easy.
I think Jung-won
is going back and forth right now.
That's enough. Don't enjoy it too much.
HE DOESN'T CARE
It's not exactly being negative.
Right. It sounds like… advice?
Yes, advice.
Maybe advice to himself?
It's advice.
CURRENT LOCATION
MOVING AGAIN
1 HOUR 12 MINUTES UNTIL SUNRISE
ENTERING THE SECTION WITH MORE SNOW
Wow, it's all snow?
-It's insane.
-I want to jump there.
-What?
Me too.
SNOWY HILL NEXT TO THE TRAIL
It's all snow.
Did someone push it here on purpose?
I think it was naturally formed.
Since people have stepped on snow here.
I think so.
THE SNOWY MOUNTAIN
IS ALSO BEAUTIFUL IN DAYLIGHT
By the way, sparkling snow
looks so beautiful.
-Right.
-When you shine the light on it.
It looks like diamonds.
There's a lot of snow.
It's so snowy.
By the way,
Jung-won is climbing pretty well.
CAR-THE'S CAM
Walking, following someone like this…
It's been ages.
When else would I follow someone?
Right? You rarely follow someone
after you become an adult.
But walking
following the producer's lantern light,
it's kind of fun.
This has been on my mind
while filming the show.
I mostly do what I can do
or what I want to do
these days.
So there aren't many situations
where I have to follow someone.
Because I only go to places I've been to
or places I can go,
not anywhere I don't know.
So I don't need to follow anyone.
I don't need anyone to guide me.
But in the mountains,
I didn't know the path.
So I had to rely
on the producer's lantern light.
It felt like I was young again.
I felt vulnerable.
I was actually weak. Yes.
When I worked at a company
or at a factory,
I used to walk a lot.
It wasn't to save money.
I just walked a lot.
I just walked without thinking.
In winter, when I went to work,
there would be a lot of snow
on my way to work.
It feels like that.
There were such days.
Now I act like I'm all that. Right?
Can I fart loudly?
Fart? Sure, go ahead.
-I did.
-I farted a lot, to be honest.
What?
Jung-won!
Should we wait a little?
Sure.
You're suddenly in good form.
THE YOUNGER ONES CATCH UP
It's uphill from now on.
CURRENT LOCATION
CAR-THE, DOWOON, TARZZAN, CHAE-MIN
Wait a second.
I think the sun's about to rise.
What?
You're right.
The sky's beginning to lighten.
What?
The sun's about to rise.
Really?
I think we should hurry up.
Let's go.
I think we're almost there.
You're right. It's getting bright.
What time is it?
Maybe 6…
Maybe 6:40 a.m.?
It should be around that.
CLIMBING THE STEEP UPHILL TRAIL
Are we taking a zipline?
Do you want to take a break
in that rest area
or keep going?
-We have to go.
-Let's just go without a break.
It's 6:44 a.m. now.
52 MINUTES UNTIL SUNRISE
The rest of the course takes an hour.
THEY ARE 8 MINUTES SHORT
THE HIGHER THE ELEVATION
THE DEEPER THE SNOW
Is this really a trail?
We're literally making a path.
Geez.
We're almost there. Hang in there.
No, I can't. Let me rest
for just 30 seconds.
When you're so tired,
you get mentally weak too.
So…
It feels like playing tag with the sun.
It's getting brighter.
As the sky began to lighten,
I was getting anxious.
I thought, "After we've come this far,
if we fail, it'll be so disappointing."
I mean, we even sacrificed sleep for this.
-Producer.
-Yes?
-I need…
-A break?
It's really bad.
-Your legs?
-Here.
-Really?
-It feels like they're tearing.
Subtitle translation by: Wayne Ryu